And there are even more tools that you can use.
These are actually very interesting,
so you can go to web extension.
It aggregates all of the Chrome extensions.
And here, what are you are going to do?
You are using one star.
And let's say one star or two stars, as you can see,
it will just narrow it down to 311, but for one.
It's like 197, and you see all of the stuff
and recently updated, and why by law rate?
Because, you know that people created some Chrome extension,
but actually, they are negative review.
So maybe the idea is great, but people who has done that.
Actually, they are not working well.
So this is the rating, VPN lighting syrup.
It didn't work well.
It's a browsing interface and all of the stuff.
And obviously, you can go to another pages
and just look for each YouTube tunnel.
Don't know that as you can see.
It's no longer working.
And if you go to Chrome extension,
you see one rating, and I don't know
that they don't exist in a file.
So how OK, this is the feedback.
And you can know actually what has been added.
And this one, boy, a web extension.
Keep that in mind.
This is the most popular.
But you can actually check by new West.
And by saying that, you will be actually
to see new applications that has been added.
Exportify, place, exporter, and there are either stuff.
As well, I found a way.
So you can use Site Chrome Web Store.
And here, what are you going to do?
You can just specify.
And last week, or a few days.
And you will be actually get some information about updated.
But I think the web extension looks a little bit better.
You have this everything aggregate.
And you have to create account, but it's for free, which is great.
So this way, you can actually create many stuff, 15,000
Chrome extensions.
So you compete with a lot of people.
But keep the demand.
Almost three billion people are using Chrome.
So you have possibility to access them.
This is the Chrome extension subreddit.
I really like it.
As you can see, you'll get some of the information,
some of the stuff you will be able to see in new projects.
This way, you can be as well up to date with all of the changes
related to creating a Chrome extension.
And if you'd like to get some information,
I would like to invite you to get maybe some cars on Udemy.
It's not my car so you can just go to Chrome extension
and try to find like web code, the Chrome extension
with cars or AI.
And this sounds interesting because I'm calling extensions.
If I-- and you will be able to do it.
So I'm adding to the cart.
And there are some even nice articles, like starter story,
how all the application action monetize the stuff.
We see extension pay with all of the statistics,
how much money I might develop in Chrome extension
from liquid, so you'll be able to do no.
This is the profile.
This is a total of $3,000.
There are even bad stories on medium.
I spent two years building a Chrome extension.
I lost $15,000, just made over $200.
So it's not always profitable.
And I would like to point it out.
This is the Chrome extension to 100K users in five years.
So this one you can actually find in many interesting articles
that we hope you up.
This is the monetization strategies
for Chrome extensions like quantum per case, subscribing,
framing model in upper cases, advertising of the eight
marketing.
And yeah, obviously we have factors to employ as a user base,
retention, niche, marketing, some examples,
how actually some big companies get so much money
and tips to maximize revenue, experience,
large leverage analytics.
So keep that in mind, try to be on time.
We follow the stuff related to here,
because it will help if all of the news,
this subreddit is very active, as you can see.
It has even this narrow, it has this arrow,
because it's growing.
And this is the greatest world to see new Chrome extension.
You can even add it as a bookmark and try to look
for a new extension.
Or like I said before, you can restart it down to one star
and see older Chrome extensions that were stopped.
So this way you can see actually which extensions
have we stopped and then you can recreate them
at some year in your future and try to monetize them.